[
  {
    "geninQuestions": [
      {
        "questionText": "What is Naruto's full name?",
        "a": "Namikaze Naruto",
        "b": "Uzumaki Naruto",
        "c": "Uchiha Naruto",
        "d": "Sarutobi Naruto",
        "correct": "b"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is Naruto's father's duty on the village",
        "a": "Ramen Chef",
        "b": "Teacher",
        "c": "Hokage",
        "d": "Messenger",
        "correct": "c"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Naruto's coin purse is a plushie of which animal?",
        "a": "Frog",
        "b": "Fox",
        "c": "Dog",
        "d": "Monkey",
        "correct": "a"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Which animal Tsunade was able to summon?",
        "a": "Frog",
        "b": "Slug",
        "c": "Snake",
        "d": "Pig",
        "correct": "b"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Who has a crush on Naruto?",
        "a": "Sakura",
        "b": "Ino",
        "c": "Tenten",
        "d": "Hinata",
        "correct": "d"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    "chuninQuestions": [
      {
        "questionText": "What is the ultimate jutsu Nagato used before he died?",
        "a": "Gedo Chibaku Tensei ",
        "b": "Gedo Shinra Tensei",
        "c": "Gedo Rinne Tensei",
        "d": "Gedo Sharin Tensei",
        "correct": "c"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Who founded Akatsuki?",
        "a": "Madara",
        "b": "Nagato",
        "c": "Yahiko",
        "d": "Jiraiya",
        "correct": "c"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is Naruto's basic chakra nature?",
        "a": "Fire",
        "b": "Wind",
        "c": "Water",
        "d": "Lightning",
        "correct": "b"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is name of Choji's clan",
        "a": "Namikaze Naruto",
        "b": "Uzumaki Naruto",
        "c": "Uchiha Naruto",
        "d": "Sarutobi Naruto",
        "correct": "b"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is the name of nine tailed beast?",
        "a": "Gyuki",
        "b": "Matatabi",
        "c": "Saiken",
        "d": "Kurama",
        "correct": "d"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    "joninQuestions": [
      {
        "questionText": "How did Danzo tried to manipulate the Kage meeting?",
        "a": "Using Izanami",
        "b": "Using Izanagi",
        "c": "Using Tsukuyomi",
        "d": "Using Koto-Amatsukami",
        "correct": "b"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Who uses the sacrificial jutsu to stop Orochimaru during Chunin Exam?",
        "a": "Kakashi",
        "b": "Hiruzen",
        "c": "Naruto",
        "d": "Sasuke",
        "correct": "b"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is Kakashi's special move which he used on Naruto during training? (Bringing his two hand together)",
        "a": "One-hundred years of Pain",
        "b": "Two-hundred years of Pain",
        "c": "One-thousand years of Pain",
        "d": "Two-thousand years of Pain",
        "correct": "c"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "How many times did Naruto fail the graduation test from the Academy?",
        "a": "Never",
        "b": "One",
        "c": "Two",
        "d": "Three",
        "correct": "d"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "How many answers did Naruto answer correctly in the first phase of the chunin exam?",
        "a": "Zero",
        "b": "One",
        "c": "Two",
        "d": "Three",
        "correct": "a"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    "anbuQuestions": [
      {
        "questionText": "After Gai defeated Kisame, who tried to extract information from Kisame?",
        "a": "Gai",
        "b": "Genma",
        "c": "Aoba",
        "d": "Kotetsu",
        "correct": "c"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is name of Choji's clan?",
        "a": "Akimichi",
        "b": "Aburame",
        "c": "Akatsuchi",
        "d": "Akamaru",
        "correct": "a"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "How old was Itachi when he graduated from the academy and became a Genin?",
        "a": "Five",
        "b": "Six",
        "c": "Seven",
        "d": "Eight",
        "correct": "c"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is the name of five tailed beast?",
        "a": "Shukaku",
        "b": "Isobu",
        "c": "Saiken",
        "d": "Kokuo",
        "correct": "d"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is the name of the puppet Kankuro carries on his back?",
        "a": "Canary",
        "b": "Crow",
        "c": "Vulture",
        "d": "Hawk",
        "correct": "b"
      }
    ]
  },

  {
    "kageQuestions": [
      {
        "questionText": "Shortly after the Chunin Exam Preliminairies, which Proctor is killed?",
        "a": "Kotetsu",
        "b": "Hayate",
        "c": "Izumo",
        "d": "Genma",
        "correct": "b"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What is Iruka's surname?",
        "a": "Ukino",
        "b": "Unimo",
        "c": "Umino",
        "d": "Ucimo",
        "correct": "c"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Who summoned the five kage for the five kage summit?",
        "a": "Hokage",
        "b": "Mizukage",
        "c": "Tsuchikage",
        "d": "Raikage",
        "correct": "d"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "How old was Kakashi when he graduated from the academy and became a Genin?",
        "a": "Five",
        "b": "Six",
        "c": "Seven",
        "d": "Eight",
        "correct": "a"
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What does the symbol on Gaara's forehead mean?",
        "a": "Hate",
        "b": "Love",
        "c": "Revenge",
        "d": "Mercy",
        "correct": "b"
      }
    ]
  }
]
